taskworld.com 2016-04-18

# Terms, Privacy & Security | Taskworld

#### Personal Information

“ **Personal Information** ,” as used in this Policy, is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as an individual’s name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. Personal Information also includes information about an individual’s activities, such as information about his or her activity on our Service, and demographic information, such as gender, geographic area, and preferences, when any of this information is linked to Personal Information that identifies that individual.

Personal Information does not include “aggregate” or other non-personal information. Aggregate information is information that we collect about a group or category of products, services, or users that is not personally identifiable or from which individual identities are removed. We may use and disclose aggregate information, and other non-personal information, for various purposes

Although information uploaded to the Service by a Taskworld enterprise customer for processing (“ **Customer Data** “) may include information that specifically identifies an individual (e.g., a Taskworld customer could upload to the Service information about its employees or other users of the Service in order to make use of the Service, including information that specifically identifies individuals such as name and email address), that information is not Personal Information for the purposes of this Policy. Please see the “Customer Data and Security” section below for information regarding Taskworld’s handling of Customer Data.

#### Collection of Information

**Collection of Voluntarily-Provided Information** We collect Personal Information that our users provide to us in a variety of ways on our Service. These include the following:

  * _E-mail Newsletters_. We may offer e-mail newsletters from time to time on our Service. If you sign up to receive a newsletter from us, we collect your e-mail address.
  * _User Accounts and Profiles_. Our Service may give you the ability to register for a Taskworld account or to create and update a user profile on the applicable Service. If we offer user account or profile functionality on the Service, we will collect the Personal Information that you provide to us in the course of registering for an account or creating or updating a user profile. This information may include, for example, name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, and related demographic information about you. We may indicate that some Personal Information is required for you to register for the account or to create the profile, while some is optional.
  * _Interactive Features_. Our Service may contain interactive functionality that allows you to engage with other users on the Service, post comments to forums, to upload photographs and other content (the “ **User Materials** “), participate in surveys, and otherwise to interact with the Service and with other users. If you use any interactive functionality on our Service that request or permit you to provide us with Personal Information (including, for example, any services that allow you to post User Materials on any of our Service), we collect the Personal Information that you provide to us in the course of using these interactive features.
  * _Correspondence_. If you contact us by e-mail, using a contact form on the Service, or by mail, fax, or other means, we collect the Personal Information contained within, and associated with, your correspondence.
  * _Contests and Sweepstakes_. We or our advertisers and other business partners may conduct or sponsor special contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions that users may enter or otherwise participate in on our Service. Certain of these promotions may be co-branded with one of our advertisers or other business partners. In these instances, the collection of your Personal Information may occur directly by the third-party partner on its website or other online service and may be shared with us. The promotion will state the privacy policy or policies governing the collection of such Personal Information.

**Passive Information Collection** When you visit our Service, some information is collected automatically. For example, when you access our Service, we may automatically collect your browser’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, the nature of the device from which you are visiting the Service (e.g., a personal computer or a mobile device), the identifier for any handheld or mobile device that you may be using, the Web site that you visited immediately prior to accessing any Web-based Service, the actions you take on our Service, and the content, features, and activities that you access and participate in on our Service. We also may collect information regarding your interaction with e-mail messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message.

We may collect this information passively using technologies such as standard server logs, cookies, and clear GIFs (also known as “Web beacons”). We use passively-collected information to administer, operate, and improve the Website and our other services and systems, to improve the effectiveness of advertising on our Service, and to provide advertisements and other content that is tailored to you.

If we link or associate any information gathered through passive means with Personal Information, or if applicable laws require us to treat any information gathered through passive means as Personal Information, we treat the combined information as Personal Information under this Policy. Otherwise, we use and disclose information collected by passive means in aggregate form or otherwise in a non-personally identifiable form.

Please be aware that in the course of your use of the Service, websites or other services provided by third parties (“ **Third-Party Services** “), including, for example, Google Analytics, may set cookies on your hard drive or use other means of passively collecting information about your use of the Service, Third-Party Services or other services or content. To do this, they may use first-party cookies (which are set by the same domain your browser is receiving data from) or third-party cookies (which are set by a different domain). Taskworld also may make non-personal information available to Third-Party Services, and these Third-Party Services may collect such information, to assist such parties in understanding our users’ activities and usage patterns on the Services.

We do not have access to, or control over, the actions of Third-Party Services. Each provider of Third-Party Services uses information that it collects in accordance with its own privacy and security policies.

With respect to Google, please be aware that we may use Google Analytics. Google, in the course of providing services or placing advertisements, may place or recognize one or more unique cookies on your computer, and may record information to these cookies based upon your activities on our Services and on third-party websites and other Third-Party Services. Google may use information about those activities to inform, optimize, and serve advertisements. Google may, for example, customize and serve advertisements on a Third-Party Service based on content you viewed on our Services. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Information from Other Sources** We may receive information about you, including Personal Information such as gender and previous place of work from third parties, such as to integrate your social media profile onto the Taskworld platform. We may combine this information with other Personal Information we maintain about you. If we do so, this Policy governs any combined information that we maintain in personally identifiable format.

**Facebook, LinkedIn, and Google Connect or Open ID** You can log in to our Web site using sign-in services such as Facebook, LinkedIn, and Google Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook, Google and LinkedIn Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

#### Information Related to Data Collected through the Taskworld Platform

Taskworld collects information under the direction of its clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes.

##### Choice

We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly.

##### Service Provider, Sub-Processors/Onward Transfer

Taskworld may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our clients

##### Access to Data Controlled by our Clients

Taskworld has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Taskworld’s client, the data controller. If the client requests Taskworld to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

##### Data Retention

Taskworld will retain personal data we process on behalf of our clients for as long as needed to provide services to our client. Taskworld will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Use of Personal Information

We use Personal Information to provide services and information that you request; to enhance, improve, operate, and maintain our Service, our programs, services, Web sites, and other systems; to prevent fraudulent use of our Service and other systems; to prevent or take action against activities that are, or may be, in violation of our Terms of Use or applicable law; to tailor advertisements, content, and other aspects of your experience on and in connection with the Service; to maintain a record of our dealings with you; for other administrative purposes; and for any other purposes that we may disclose to you at the point at which we request your Personal Information, and pursuant to your consent.

We may also use Personal Information you provide to contact you regarding products, services, and offers, both from ourselves and from third parties, that we believe you may find of interest. We allow you to opt-out from receiving marketing communications from us as described in the “Choice” section below. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Taskworld.

#### Disclosure of Personal Information

Except as described in this Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information that we collect on the Service to third parties without your consent. We may disclose information to third parties if you consent to us doing so, as well as in the following circumstances:

**Enterprise Administrators** The Service permits the administrator of an enterprise account to access all information submitted by the enterprise’s end users, including information about contacts that you choose to upload to the Service and your Personal Information.

**Service Providers** We may disclose Personal Information to third-party service providers (e.g., payment processing and data storage and processing facilities) that assist us in our work. We limit the Personal Information provided to these service providers to that which is reasonably necessary for them to perform their functions, and we require them to agree to maintain the confidentiality of such Personal Information.

**Public Areas** Some features on our Service may allow you to upload, post, or otherwise transmit User Materials to public areas of the Service, such as content that you post in a public profile on the Service. Please be aware that any Personal Information that you include within any User Materials will be made available to other users of the Service. You include Personal Information in User Materials at your sole risk. We may allow you to select privacy options that limit access to some types of Personal Information in User Materials, but no security measures are impenetrable or perfect. Additionally, even after information posted on the Website is removed, caching and archiving services may have saved that information, and other users or third parties may have copied or stored the information available on the Service. We cannot warrant or guarantee that any Personal Information that you provide on and in connection with the Service will not be accessed, viewed, or used by unauthorized persons.

**Business Transfers** Information about our users, including Personal Information, may be disclosed and otherwise transferred to an acquirer, or successor or assignee as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of Taskworld assets, or similar transaction, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which Personal Information is transferred to one or more third parties as one of our business assets.

**To Protect our Interests** We also disclose Personal Information if we believe that doing so is legally required, or is in our interest to protect our property or other legal rights (including, but not limited to, enforcement of our agreements), or the rights or property of others, or otherwise to help protect the safety or security of our Service and other users of the Service.

#### Choice

If you subscribe to our newsletter(s) or receive commercial e-mail from us, you may unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions contained within the e-mail. You may also opt-out from receiving commercial e-mail from us, and any other promotional communications that we may send to you from time to time (e.g., by postal mail) by sending your request to us by e-mail at [privacy@taskworld.com](mailto:privacy@taskworld.com) or by writing to us at the address given at the end of this policy. Additionally, if we offer user account functionality on the Service, we may allow you to view and modify settings relating to the nature and frequency of promotional communications that you receive from us.

Please be aware that if you opt-out of receiving commercial e-mail from us, it may take up to ten business days for us to process your opt-out request, and you may receive commercial e-mail from us during that period. Additionally, even after you opt-out from receiving commercial messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding our Service.

#### Access

If we offer the ability to create user accounts or profiles on our Service, you may have the ability to access and update many categories of Personal Information that you provide to us by logging in to your account and accessing your account settings. If you wish to access, delete or amend any other Personal Information we hold about you, you may contact us at[privacy@taskworld.com](mailto:privacy@taskworld.com).

If you request that we delete your account on any of our Service (via a user settings page, by e-mail, or otherwise), we will do so within a reasonable period of time, but we may need to retain some of your Personal Information in order to satisfy our legal obligations, or where we reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so.

#### Links

The Service may contain links to other Web sites, products, or services that we do not own or operate. For example, the Service may contain links to third-party merchants from which users may purchase sound recordings that are streamed through the Service. The Service also may contain links to Third-Party Sites such as social networking services. If you choose to visit or use any Third-Party Sites or products or services available on or through such Third-Party Sites, please be aware that this Policy will not apply to your activities or any information you disclose while using those Third-Party Sites or any products or services available on or through such Third-Party Sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these Third-Party Sites or any products or services on or through them. Additionally, please be aware that the Service may contain links to Web sites and services that we operate but that are governed by different privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies applicable to any Web site or service you visit other than the Service before providing any Personal Information on them.

#### Social Media Widgets

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook and Twitters buttons and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social media features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Children

Children’s safety is important to us, and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active interest in the online activities of their children. Our Service is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 without obtaining parental consent. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13 on our Service, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we may have collected any such Personal Information on our Service, please notify us at [privacy@taskworld.com](mailto:privacy@taskworld.com).

#### International Visitors

Our servers and data centers are located in the United States. If you choose to use the Service from outside the U.S., then you should know that you are transferring your Personal Information outside of your region and into the U.S. for storage and processing. By providing your Personal Information to us through your use of the Service, you agree to that transfer, storage, and processing in the U.S. Also, we may transfer your data from the U.S. to other countries or regions in connection with storage and processing of data, fulfilling your requests, and operating the Service. You should know that each region can have its own privacy and data security laws, some of which may be less stringent as compared to those of your own region.

#### Customer Data and Security

Taskworld enterprise customers may electronically submit Customer Data to the Service. Taskworld will not review, share, distribute, or reference any Customer Data except for providing the Service to that enterprise customer and its authorized users, preventing or addressing service or technical problems, at the enterprise customer’s request in connection with customer support matters, or as may be required by law.

We use reasonable security measures that are designed to protect Personal Information and Customer Data from accidental loss, disclosure, misuse, and destruction. These measures may include regular review of our data collection and storage processes, data encryption, and security software on our networks and servers. Please be aware, however, that no data security measures can be guaranteed to be completely effective. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you, including enterprise customers, provide to us. You transmit information to us at your own risk.

#### Updates to this Policy

We may occasionally update this Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the beginning of the Policy. Your continued use of our Service after such changes will be subject to the then-current policy. If we change this Policy in a manner that is materially less restrictive of our use or disclosure of your Personal Information, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the change via email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) and to obtain your consent prior to applying the change to any Personal Information that we collected from you prior to the date the change becomes effective. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to stay informed about how we collect, use, and disclose Personal Information.
